Rachel Burra

Ex-Financial Analyst, Content Freelancer

Mumbai, India +(91) 8790409426 rachel.nikita9@gmail.com

Experienced and effective Financial Analyst transitioned to content freelancing bringing forth valuable experience and a passion for content. Adept in analytical thinking, data analysis and reporting, and building business relationships.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance- Upwork, Freelancer.com etc.

Jul 2022- present

Content writing, copywriting and editing for B2B business clients, websites.

ICICI BANK, Mumbai — Financial Planning Analyst

Jun 2018 - Jul 2022

- Drove monitoring and reporting of key business drivers/ metrics
- Analyzed sales and financial performance to effectively plan for future opportunities, while identifying obvious weak trends
- Advised internal teams on implications of business trends, operating environment changes, and business strategy
- Identified and implemented process re-engineering initiatives including dashboard automation for CFO
- Drove forward looking processes including forecasts, operating plans and business outlook

GOLDMAN SACHS, Bangalore—Summer Analyst

Apr 2017 - May 2017

- End-to-end creation and delivery of global interactive dashboard for employee metrics tracking
- Research and implementation of Supervisors Systems enhancements to optimize visibility and efficiency

EDUCATION

University of Mumbai, Mumbai — Masters in Finance

Apr 2016 - Apr 2018

- GPA 5.92/7
- National Finalist (Indus Valley Campus Challenge)
- Financial Inclusion Outreach Program coordinator

SKILLS

Financial Planning

Data Analysis

Content

Operations

Microsoft Excel

Osmania University, Hyderabad— Bachelors in Management Studies

Apr 2012 - Apr 2015